results = [
    {"question": "You have asked for a \"radio check\" as you believe that your radio may be transmitting an unclear signal. A station replies back that they hear you \"strength 3\". This means that your transmission is;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Readable now and then", "correctAnswer": "Readable but with difficulty", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(m)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:34:45.560334", "incorrectAnswer2": "Readable", "id": "616eb4d9-3893-4a99-ae45-46533e7c1f32", "incorrectAnswer3": "Perfectly readable"}, {"question": "What is the most important to remember when entering a squawk code into the transponder?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Not to accidentally select 1300, 1400, or 2200.", "correctAnswer": "Not to accidentally select 7500, 7600, or 7700.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.2", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 09:04:13.459399", "incorrectAnswer2": "Ensure the transponder squelch is set correctly.", "id": "5bb5acd1-4084-4cd0-9621-a0606e4cb634", "incorrectAnswer3": "The code 1200 should always be entered when flying VFR."}, {"question": "What causes an Emergency Locator Transmitter (ELT) to activate automatically?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Setting the transponder code to 7700.", "correctAnswer": "High g-force/rapid deceleration, and in some cases immersion in water.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.6(a)", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 02:42:50.044447", "incorrectAnswer2": "Setting the ELT remote switch to \"ON\".", "id": "4effa1ab-affb-4f8a-ba44-b12bf3cabc6c", "incorrectAnswer3": "If any carbon monoxide is detected by the cockpit CO detector."}, {"question": "How would you select Mode C on a transponder?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Select the \"ON\" setting.", "correctAnswer": "Select the \"ALT\" (altitude) setting.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.2", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 09:12:13.541940", "incorrectAnswer2": "Select the \"STBY\" (standby) setting.", "id": "3c72b509-d572-47f1-99ae-b7f0c9fce3cc", "incorrectAnswer3": "Select the \"TST\" (test) setting."}, {"question": "You are flying in controlled transponder mandatory airspace and notice the display on your transponder has gone dark and appears to have failed. You try turning it off and on, and check the circuit-breaker, but the transponder remains off. What should you do?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Immediately depart the controlled airspace", "correctAnswer": "Notify the ATC unit with jurisdiction over the relevant airspace", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 22:57:06.629061", "incorrectAnswer2": "Squawk 7600", "id": "e942edb3-6d2a-42f4-bfb3-23f6f24d856e", "incorrectAnswer3": "Transmit a MAYDAY call"}, {"question": "A control tower issues you an instruction to \"Track direct to the racecourse.\"  You are unable to do so without entering cloud. What should you do?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Transmit: \"Track direct to the racecourse due cloud.\"", "correctAnswer": "Transmit: \"Unable to track direct to the racecourse due cloud.\"", "syllabusReference": "2.12.2(a)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:36:13.166369", "incorrectAnswer2": "Transmit: \"Track direct to the racecourse not available.\"", "id": "bc71aba4-8916-48e3-a607-32351c571d5d", "incorrectAnswer3": "Transmit: \"Wilco.\""}, {"question": "Where can you find aerodrome frequencies?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "On Visual Planning and Visual Navigation Charts only.", "correctAnswer": "In AIPNZ Vol 4, and on Visual Planning and Visual Navigation Charts (VPCs and VNCs).", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(g)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:09:32.024838", "incorrectAnswer2": "On Visual Planning and Visual Navigation Charts (VPCs and VNCs), and Terminal Aerodrome Forecasts (TAFs).", "id": "5ff513bd-7615-46aa-b628-abd685152b57", "incorrectAnswer3": "In AIPNZ Vol 4, and Notices to Airmen (NOTAMs)."}, {"question": "How can you identify airspace where a transponder is required?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "On an aerodrome plate, denoted by the term \"position transmitting equipment required.\"", "correctAnswer": "On a Visual Navigation Chart (VNC), denoted by the letters \"TM\".", "syllabusReference": "2.6.10", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 09:17:37.928624", "incorrectAnswer2": "A transponder is required in all airspace in the NZ FIR.", "id": "428733cc-d3fb-41bf-bfc8-5b1cd14d8e7b", "incorrectAnswer3": "By checking the conditions required for entry into a MOA."}, {"question": "You're approaching an aerodrome with an inoperative radio. You see a series of red flashes from the light gun, meaning...", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Give way to other aircraft and continue circling", "correctAnswer": "Aerodrome unsafe, do not land", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:44:56.610850", "incorrectAnswer2": "Danger, be on the alert", "id": "327cfb49-ee6d-4ed4-a9a2-f475da6ceb14", "incorrectAnswer3": "Return for landing (clearance to land and taxi will be given in due course)"}, {"question": "What is the correct phrase to use if you are unable to understand all or part of a transmission and would like the sender to repeat it?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Please repeat.", "correctAnswer": "Say again.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(d)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:38:13.169250", "incorrectAnswer2": "Unable to understand, repeat.", "id": "bf887545-43a3-44c5-a5a9-ecc237e16ee9", "incorrectAnswer3": "I read you 2."}, {"question": "A MAYDAY call should be made if you encounter what sort of situation?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "You or someone else are in possible danger and require immediate assistance", "correctAnswer": "You or someone else are in imminent danger and require immediate assistance", "syllabusReference": "2.14.2(a)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:37:15.882109", "incorrectAnswer2": "You or someone else are in possible danger but do not require immediate assistance", "id": "ab2cfc8d-958e-48f7-b11e-aa1cb4a67d01", "incorrectAnswer3": "You or someone else are in imminent danger but do not require immediate assistance"}, {"question": "What is the correct pronunciation of \"9\" in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Nine", "correctAnswer": "Niner", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(c)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:18:38.886596", "incorrectAnswer2": "Nin", "id": "09a12827-142d-4398-b6a5-012afdadaa29", "incorrectAnswer3": "Nought"}, {"question": "What does the term \"WILCO\" mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "I have received all of your previous transmission.", "correctAnswer": "I understand your message and will comply with it.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(d)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:40:09.173567", "incorrectAnswer2": "Will continue with the previous ATC instruction.", "id": "90c61950-dc30-4690-bdb0-f9fe2de899e5", "incorrectAnswer3": "I am unable to comply with your previous transmission."}, {"question": "If you set mode Alpha on your transponder then;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "the transponder will be in standby mode", "correctAnswer": "it will not transmit any altitude information", "syllabusReference": "2.6.4(a)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:30:45.453157", "incorrectAnswer2": "it will transmit only the aircraft True Airspeed", "id": "e0645760-c1e6-496c-b0a7-bdb7c3827db3", "incorrectAnswer3": "it will transmit only the aircraft Indicated Airspeed"}, {"question": "When is it allowed to omit the \"ZK-\" from a callsign? eg. for ZK-LJF this would be \"Lima-Juliet-Foxtrot\".", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "During high workload times only.", "correctAnswer": "When the ground station has used this callsign and it's unlikely to cause confusion with other aircraft.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(i)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:20:33.764343", "incorrectAnswer2": "When the controller requests the aircraft use their full callsign.", "id": "e369c066-dd56-47f2-b07c-3b2485dd0e51", "incorrectAnswer3": "When flying under radar control."}, {"question": "What does the term \"ROGER\" mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "I will comply with your last transmission.", "correctAnswer": "I have received all of your last transmission.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(d)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:35:59.451685", "incorrectAnswer2": "This is the end of my transmission.", "id": "8871fdc5-c50a-464a-981c-77db2e98c187", "incorrectAnswer3": "\"Yes\"."}, {"question": "You carry out a forced landing into a paddock within New Zealand and no radio or phone coverage is available. The symbol you would use to indicate to any aircraft overhead that you are fine and that no immediate help is required, is;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "a smiley face", "correctAnswer": "LL", "syllabusReference": "2.10.10", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:35:38.698778", "incorrectAnswer2": "XX", "id": "0bcd06a5-4cab-4a5c-ac56-970306b403c7", "incorrectAnswer3": "XXX"}, {"question": "If your ELT has inadvertently been activated, what is the correct procedure for disarming the ELT?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Turn the ELT switch to ARM for up to 5 seconds, then back to ON. Notify ATC and the RCCNZ as soon as possible.", "correctAnswer": "Turn the ELT switch to ON for up to 5 seconds, then back to ARM. Notify ATC and the RCCNZ as soon as possible. ", "syllabusReference": "2.8.12", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 01:00:16.110083", "incorrectAnswer2": "The ELT will automatically deactivate if no impact is detected within 5 minutes. Notify ATC and RCCNZ as soon as possible.", "id": "13422462-ec6f-48da-9d09-f9b331efde19", "incorrectAnswer3": "Squawk 1200 and notify ATC of the inadvertent activation."}, {"question": "What is the correct term to indicate \"No\"?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "No", "correctAnswer": "Negative", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(d)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:41:39.476511", "incorrectAnswer2": "Standby", "id": "58f49356-5556-4b7c-bf62-54c590d879dd", "incorrectAnswer3": "Roger"}, {"question": "If you weren't able to understand a radio transmission, what is the correct phrase to request the sender to repeat themselves?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "CORRECTION", "correctAnswer": "SAY AGAIN", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(k)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:26:51.978563", "incorrectAnswer2": "PLEASE REPEAT", "id": "09071976-0705-4120-9329-39273eb0781a", "incorrectAnswer3": "MISUNDERSTOOD"}, {"question": "What is the transponder code 2000 used for?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "All aircraft when operating in the aerodrome traffic circuit at a controlled aerodrome", "correctAnswer": "All IFR traffic, and VFR traffic operating in the Auckland Oceanic FIR only", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:06:05.691258", "incorrectAnswer2": "Defence aeroplanes", "id": "5b985ac9-8a80-4b11-987d-12ac08a3dc49", "incorrectAnswer3": "Gliders or balloons"}, {"question": "What does Readability Two mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Unreadable", "correctAnswer": "Readable now and then", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(m)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:42:40.395846", "incorrectAnswer2": "Readable, but with difficulty", "id": "967fa661-ba7c-442e-9eed-17a86281e810", "incorrectAnswer3": "Readable"}, {"question": "A disadvantage of Very High Frequency (VHF) signals are that they", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "are more susceptible to static interference than HF signals", "correctAnswer": "are limited to line-of-sight", "syllabusReference": "2.2.2(a)", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 09:24:14.835811", "incorrectAnswer2": "require radio equipment only available on modern aircraft", "id": "612c0faa-b012-4880-9f38-50cc427933e8", "incorrectAnswer3": "can be disturbed by sky waves, causing a loss of reception"}, {"question": "When are you able to self-test an ELT?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "In the first 5 minutes after the hour, for a maximum of 5 siren sweeps.", "correctAnswer": "In the first 5 minutes after the hour, for a maximum of 3 siren sweeps.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.10", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 00:50:57.204228", "incorrectAnswer2": "In the last 5 minutes before the hour, for a maximum of 3 siren sweeps.", "id": "73bd8c6b-4cf4-4999-9b53-a562d20e8f9d", "incorrectAnswer3": "Any time as long as the ELT is in the ARM position."}, {"question": "A transponder code of 7500 indicates", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "a loss of communications", "correctAnswer": "a hijacking", "syllabusReference": "2.6.6", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:31:08.174469", "incorrectAnswer2": "an emergency situation, such as an engine failure", "id": "057bf78f-c378-4ec9-a29b-3f8360f64391", "incorrectAnswer3": "an urgency situation, which does not involve immediate danger to those in the air or on the ground"}, {"question": "When operating in Class A airspace...", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Two-way communications are required with the ATC unit responsible for the airspace, unless flying on an IFR flight plan.", "correctAnswer": "Two-way communications are required with the ATC unit responsible for the airspace, unless authorised.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(c)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:32:15.543820", "incorrectAnswer2": "Two-way communications are always required with the ATC unit responsible for the airspace.", "id": "1b17194b-3729-4e96-baa6-aed4e7ea1be0", "incorrectAnswer3": "Two-way communications are required with the ATC unit responsible for the airspace, unless flying an aircraft equipped with dual ADSB transmitters."}, {"question": "To increase the range of your radio transmissions, you could fly;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Lower", "correctAnswer": "Higher", "syllabusReference": "2.2.2(a)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:26:40.407592", "incorrectAnswer2": "Slower", "id": "17aed01f-d9f8-4a0d-abdd-ef1a0b855a80", "incorrectAnswer3": "Faster"}, {"question": "How should the letter \"Z\" be said in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Zebra", "correctAnswer": "Zulu", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:14:21.045192", "incorrectAnswer2": "Zee", "id": "13d3dc5e-48db-4d4d-a4cc-3c4168b81b0f", "incorrectAnswer3": "Zealand"}, {"question": "You're ferrying an aircraft with an inoperative ELT to an airport where it can be repaired. What restriction applies?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "The flight must not be over mountainous terrain.", "correctAnswer": "You can't take any passengers.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.4", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 02:29:43.740478", "incorrectAnswer2": "The departure and destination airfields must be within 50 nm of each other.", "id": "521dc883-4cf2-4169-9844-8738bfcb8ff6", "incorrectAnswer3": "The aircraft must not have more than 4 seats."}, {"question": "The frequencies to be used when TIBA is activated can be found in which source?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Visual Navigation Charts", "correctAnswer": "NZ AIP Volume 4", "syllabusReference": "2.18.4(a)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:42:19.128402", "incorrectAnswer2": "Instrument Navigation Charts", "id": "f7bffa2a-ded0-468c-9f3e-45c58802a787", "incorrectAnswer3": "Aerodrome Charts"}, {"question": "What frequency/frequencies does an ELT transmit on?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "121.5 MHz only.", "correctAnswer": "121.5 MHz and 406 MHz.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.2", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 02:02:43.771608", "incorrectAnswer2": "111.00 MHz and 406 MHz.", "id": "f74f2f40-1bbc-4c57-9c07-7daa5e014751", "incorrectAnswer3": "406 MHz only."}, {"question": "What transponder code should be used by gliders and balloons, unless otherwise assigned a code by ATC?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "1200", "correctAnswer": "1300", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:06:43.294215", "incorrectAnswer2": "2000", "id": "144396a4-0bae-47b7-9890-90bf759d2ce6", "incorrectAnswer3": "0111"}, {"question": "The two-seat Cessna 152 you've rented to practice circuits in has an inoperative ELT. Are you able to go ahead with the flight?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "No, the only flight that would be allowed is a ferry flight to have the ELT fixed.", "correctAnswer": "Yes, an Aircraft Emergency Location System (AELS) isn't required on a two-seat aircraft if operating within 10 nm of the aerodrome it took off from.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.4", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 02:25:05.960927", "incorrectAnswer2": "Yes, an ELT is only required if carrying more than one person.", "id": "1e40017b-e3a8-4e12-842e-355a268fde45", "incorrectAnswer3": "No, an ELT is always required in the New Zealand Flight Information Region (NZ FIR)."}, {"question": "What is the correct way to transmit the time 11:30pm?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Eleven thirty pee em", "correctAnswer": "Two tree tree zero", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(e)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:58:48.421197", "incorrectAnswer2": "One one tree zero", "id": "838a2dc4-b610-438b-b7bf-086a7a84ad48", "incorrectAnswer3": "Twenty-three tree zero"}, {"question": "The High Frequency (HF) band is commonly used", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "for short distance communication", "correctAnswer": "for long distance communication", "syllabusReference": "2.2.2(a)", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 09:14:32.762022", "incorrectAnswer2": "in turboprop aircraft", "id": "89cf57f5-fc7e-4d52-9fcf-b87787723e25", "incorrectAnswer3": "as a backup to VHF communication"}, {"question": "When radio silence is imposed following a MAYDAY call, this must be observed by all other stations until;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "the pilot in command of the aircraft that transmitted the MAYDAY allows stations to transmit", "correctAnswer": "the controlling station allows normal transmissions", "syllabusReference": "2.14.4(b)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:37:44.712290", "incorrectAnswer2": "there has been a continuous period of 5 minutes or longer without any transmissions related to the MAYDAY situation", "id": "e7eb40b2-b6f6-4002-8513-aeaa24b3a0a2", "incorrectAnswer3": "there has been a continuous period of 10 minutes or longer without any transmissions related to the MAYDAY situation"}, {"question": "What language must be used to make a radio call?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "French", "correctAnswer": "English", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(a)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:06:58.558330", "incorrectAnswer2": "The language of the country the aircraft is operated in", "id": "9a93d3f7-2345-43b1-834d-7410fa6cc7b5", "incorrectAnswer3": "The language of the country of aircraft manufacture"}, {"question": "A transponder code of 7700 indicates", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "an urgency situation, which does not involve immediate danger to those in the air or on the ground", "correctAnswer": "an emergency situation, such as an engine failure", "syllabusReference": "2.6.6", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 10:18:55.477338", "incorrectAnswer2": "a loss of communications", "id": "4a027ddc-e9a4-4166-83fb-29ac1ba04501", "incorrectAnswer3": "a hijacking"}, {"question": "Part 91 requires New Zealand registered aircraft to carry an Aircraft Emergency Location System (AELS) at all times when flying in the New Zealand Flight Information Region (NZ FIR) with some exceptions. Which of these is a valid exception?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "During day VFR below 10,000 ft AMSL.", "correctAnswer": "Ferry flights from where an operator takes possession of an aircraft to a place where the AELS is to be installed.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.4", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 02:18:10.012045", "incorrectAnswer2": "When flying in non-mountainous terrain.", "id": "ce475b24-8c50-4486-bc38-22d4aa8baa9e", "incorrectAnswer3": "When flying within 25 NM of the departure aerodrome."}, {"question": "When can an aircraft without an operable transponder operate in Transponder Mandatory airspace?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "When transiting in accordance with VFR cruising altitudes.", "correctAnswer": "With prior ATC approval, and complying with any conditions of that approval.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.12", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 09:21:54.549287", "incorrectAnswer2": "When maintaining a visual lookout for other traffic, where the pilot in command is responsible for separation.", "id": "6716d92c-62df-44e7-ab01-37109ae38c61", "incorrectAnswer3": "After notifying ATC."}, {"question": "What is the correct pronunciation of \"3\" in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Three", "correctAnswer": "Tree", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2.(c)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:16:55.121340", "incorrectAnswer2": "Thrie", "id": "a01cd5fa-363f-494f-81b0-f544456e821e", "incorrectAnswer3": "Free"}, {"question": "What transponder code means \"Unlawful interference\" (hijack)?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "7600", "correctAnswer": "7500", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:11:31.783250", "incorrectAnswer2": "7700", "id": "d63327c8-2376-4324-9788-7eceea406089", "incorrectAnswer3": "1200"}, {"question": "How should the letter \"H\" be said in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Aych", "correctAnswer": "Hotel", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:12:00.484015", "incorrectAnswer2": "Henry", "id": "b033a866-e201-4a96-835e-831ef34fef7e", "incorrectAnswer3": "Hornet"}, {"question": "What does Readability Five mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Readable", "correctAnswer": "Perfectly readable", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(m)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:44:28.979994", "incorrectAnswer2": "Readable, but with difficulty", "id": "8438cd51-7806-4484-a558-2d91ceb74bf9", "incorrectAnswer3": "Readable now and then"}, {"question": "What is the transponder code 0111 used for?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "All aircraft when operating in the aerodrome traffic circuit at a controlled aerodrome", "correctAnswer": "Aircraft involved in fire fighting and reconnaissance duties", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:05:07.250588", "incorrectAnswer2": "Helicopters other than Defence helicopters", "id": "a3bd2003-98a2-42ba-b50e-01cdbccdc780", "incorrectAnswer3": "Gliders or balloons"}, {"question": "What is the correct method of operation for a handheld microphone?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Place the handheld microphone in its cradle, press the Push To Talk (PTT) button on the microphone, transmit your message, and release the PTT button", "correctAnswer": "Hold the microphone close to your mouth, press the Push To Talk (PTT) button on the microphone, transmit your message, and release the PTT button", "syllabusReference": "2.4.4(b)", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 10:15:24.092763", "incorrectAnswer2": "Hold the microphone close to your mouth, press the Push To Talk (PTT) button on the control yoke, transmit your message, and release the PTT button", "id": "d9fc9579-498a-480d-98bc-08210a391470", "incorrectAnswer3": "Hold the microphone close to your mouth, click the Push To Talk (PTT) once to activate the transmission, transmit your message, then click the PTT button again to end the transmission"}, {"question": "When is it generally recommended to turn on the aircraft radio?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Before engine start to ensure any transmissions from taxiing aircraft can be heard", "correctAnswer": "After engine start, to prevent the radio being damaged by voltage spikes during engine start", "syllabusReference": "2.4.2", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 10:04:02.438796", "incorrectAnswer2": "As late as possible immediately prior to taxi, to prevent the aircraft battery from being drained", "id": "29c5ea6e-d6ab-485e-8243-f900921c9fec", "incorrectAnswer3": "As soon as you enter the aircraft"}, {"question": "If ATC instructs you to \"SQUAWK ALTITUDE\", what should you do?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Set the transponder to \"ON\" (Mode A).", "correctAnswer": "Set the transponder to \"ALT\" (Mode C).", "syllabusReference": "2.6.8", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 09:27:13.735873", "incorrectAnswer2": "Set the transponder to \"ON\" (Mode C).", "id": "f6d7009d-3cf2-4829-a22f-ef8abebb746a", "incorrectAnswer3": "Set the transponder to \"ALT\" (Mode A)."}, {"question": "While flying you want to talk to a control tower but discover there is no reception on the frequency your radio is tuned to. You have checked you have the correct frequency set. What should you do next?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Squawk ident", "correctAnswer": "Check the squelch level", "syllabusReference": "2.4.2", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:29:40.851964", "incorrectAnswer2": "Change from VHF to HF for that frequency", "id": "e603f2c9-41ed-4a95-9a10-1506be412a52", "incorrectAnswer3": "Tune the radio to the local VOR frequency"}, {"question": "What transponder code is used by Defence aeroplanes?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "1200", "correctAnswer": "6000", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:10:17.806816", "incorrectAnswer2": "2200", "id": "d818ae5c-fdd9-4131-b499-d1147aa0d976", "incorrectAnswer3": "6500"}, {"question": "You're flying in controlled airspace under visual flight rules (VFR) and notice the screen on your transponder has gone blank. What should you do?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "No action is required if flying in controlled airspace under VFR.", "correctAnswer": "Immediately advise ATC.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.12", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 01:57:05.584812", "incorrectAnswer2": "Squawk 7600.", "id": "fd56bbac-0139-48e0-b5ba-9bb041816f4c", "incorrectAnswer3": "Push the ident button to alert ATC."}, {"question": "When flying low in mountainous terrain, not in the vicinity of a repeater station", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "VHF signals are more likely to be received than HF signals because HF signals require line of sight", "correctAnswer": "HF signals are more likely to be received than VHF signals because VHF signals require line-of-sight", "syllabusReference": "2.2.2(b)", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 09:31:56.951405", "incorrectAnswer2": "you should always adhere to TIBA procedures", "id": "c72cbf6f-c31c-4123-9bd5-ce83429a420e", "incorrectAnswer3": "VHF signals are likely to be received in the lee of a mountain range, relative to the broadcast antenna"}, {"question": "If you make a mistake during a radio call, what should you say before transmitting the correct message?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "MISTAKE", "correctAnswer": "CORRECTION", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(k)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:25:58.576737", "incorrectAnswer2": "I SAY AGAIN", "id": "f796da90-cfb5-47ab-b177-8693568f6e93", "incorrectAnswer3": "ALTERATION"}, {"question": "What is the correct pronunciation of \"4\" in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Four", "correctAnswer": "Fow-er", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(c)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:17:49.605761", "incorrectAnswer2": "Floor", "id": "216b991f-3d70-425f-9c91-bb56b419bd3c", "incorrectAnswer3": "Fort"}, {"question": "How should the letter \"P\" be said in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Piper", "correctAnswer": "Papa", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:12:30.902082", "incorrectAnswer2": "Pee", "id": "189d3dc9-d151-4dc8-acab-16860406a348", "incorrectAnswer3": "Peter"}, {"question": "In the phonetic alphabet, the word QUIZ is spelt;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Quazar - Uruguay - India - Zulu", "correctAnswer": "Quebec - Uniform - India - Zulu", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(b)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:31:54.054361", "incorrectAnswer2": "Quest - Uruguay - India - Zoo", "id": "14955363-9d6f-4a74-957f-4ae81dd2d0ef", "incorrectAnswer3": "Quest - Uniform - India - Zulu"}, {"question": "What does the transponder code 7600 mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Unlawful interference (hijack)", "correctAnswer": "Loss of radio communication", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:12:45.837703", "incorrectAnswer2": "In flight emergency, when no code has been allocated by ATC", "id": "449c12f4-44c2-4a15-ac59-8f28aecb02a0", "incorrectAnswer3": "Aircraft operating in traffic circuit at a controlled aerodrome"}, {"question": "A transponder code of 7600 indicates", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "an emergency situation, such as an engine failure", "correctAnswer": "a loss of communications", "syllabusReference": "2.6.6", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 10:18:31.118954", "incorrectAnswer2": "an urgency situation, which does not involve immediate danger to those in the air or on the ground", "id": "81763d78-4a53-48a7-9134-5f762020fb1f", "incorrectAnswer3": "a hijacking"}, {"question": "You're in the air with an inop radio. You have been circling when you see a series of green flashes from the tower's light gun. What does this mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Cleared to land", "correctAnswer": "Return for landing (clearance to land and taxi will be given in due course)", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:43:44.371122", "incorrectAnswer2": "Land at this aerodrome and proceed to apron", "id": "1b0d357a-abad-496e-8297-7b84ed2ed34b", "incorrectAnswer3": "Danger, be on the alert"}, {"question": "The majority of General Aviation aircraft use a", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "High Frequency (HF) radio, which has better clarity than a Very High Frequency (VHF) radio", "correctAnswer": "Very High Frequency (VHF) radio, which has better clarity than a High Frequency (HF) radio", "syllabusReference": "2.2.2(c)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:27:21.109277", "incorrectAnswer2": "Low Frequency (LF) radio, which has better clarity than a High Frequency (HF) radio", "id": "ad520bca-d626-4f5d-a7f1-f5ebe8f834ce", "incorrectAnswer3": "Very Low Frequency (VLF) radio, which has better clarity than a Very High Frequency (VHF) radio"}, {"question": "While flying, over the aviation radio you hear about the crash of an aircraft and the name of the pilot is discussed. Which statement is correct?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "You may not divulge the pilot's name if no other sources are able to verify the information", "correctAnswer": "You may not divulge the pilot's name to anyone", "syllabusReference": "2.12.4(b)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:36:54.405953", "incorrectAnswer2": "You may divulge the pilot's name if they are uninjured", "id": "95dd3464-9990-4699-b7cd-42d7b41782f9", "incorrectAnswer3": "You may divulge the pilot's name to their relatives"}, {"question": "In an aircraft where occupants are wearing headsets with boom microphones, activating the Push To Talk (PTT) button", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "will transmit the microphone signals from all occupants", "correctAnswer": "will transmit only the microphone signal of the person in the same seating position as the PTT being pressed", "syllabusReference": "2.4.4(a)", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 09:59:14.741822", "incorrectAnswer2": "allows occupants of the aircraft to hear each other through their headsets", "id": "2ffe2313-eac6-4ab8-ab08-b2dd2361c55f", "incorrectAnswer3": "transmits microphone signals from only occupants in the front seats"}, {"question": "You're part of a formation entering transponder mandatory airspace. Who is required to have an operating transponder (unless otherwise required by ATC)?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "All aircraft in the formation", "correctAnswer": "Only one aircraft in the formation", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 22:59:54.695963", "incorrectAnswer2": "Only the lead and tail aircraft of the formation", "id": "718f2b62-2a99-4ed8-b8d8-f2aa9696d297", "incorrectAnswer3": "Formation flights don't require transponders given the large radar return"}, {"question": "If your microphone was broken in flight but you could still hear and transmit, how would you answer \"Yes\" to a question asked by an ATS unit?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Activate the transmitter twice", "correctAnswer": "Activate the transmitter once", "syllabusReference": "2.16.8", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:39:45.864557", "incorrectAnswer2": "Activate the transmitter three times", "id": "55fcff2a-ce9e-4e56-b54b-c78712a0a060", "incorrectAnswer3": "Activate the transmitter four times"}, {"question": "An Emergency Locator Transmitter should only be tested;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "during the first 30 minutes of each hour, and for a maximum of three siren sweeps", "correctAnswer": "during the first 5 minutes of each hour, and for a maximum of three siren sweeps", "syllabusReference": "2.8.10", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:31:35.058359", "incorrectAnswer2": "during the first 5 minutes of each hour, and for a maximum of 30 seconds", "id": "18cf10e7-ba8c-4b8b-8278-99db9363cdbd", "incorrectAnswer3": "during the first 5 minutes of each hour, and for a maximum of 15 seconds"}, {"question": "Which of the following statements is true about communicating the time in radio transmissions?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Hours and minutes should always be transmitted.", "correctAnswer": "Only minutes are normally required, unless there is any possibility of misunderstanding, in which case the hour should also be included.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(e)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:52:56.436523", "incorrectAnswer2": "Time transmitted in minutes is always referenced to the previous hour.", "id": "279dd175-7f60-41d8-b150-6f92ec1d95e9", "incorrectAnswer3": "Time transmitted in minutes is always referenced to the next hour."}, {"question": "You have previously made a PAN PAN call but now wish to cancel that call. What words must your transmission to cancel the call include?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "PAN PAN resolved", "correctAnswer": "Cancel PAN PAN", "syllabusReference": "2.14.8", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:38:10.203304", "incorrectAnswer2": "Negative PAN PAN", "id": "50947832-5724-4780-9e99-2b710b2b3fab", "incorrectAnswer3": "All Stations, PAN PAN situation no longer applies"}, {"question": "Can an aircraft fly in uncontrolled transponder mandatory airspace if the aircraft is only equipped with a Mode A transponder?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "No", "correctAnswer": "Yes", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 22:53:05.993526", "incorrectAnswer2": "Only if the transponder is also transmitting ADS-B OUT messages", "id": "ca9f0a1d-0e49-48c6-aec0-e8e179b82b4c", "incorrectAnswer3": "Yes, but only within 10 NM of the departure aerodrome"}, {"question": "ATC instructions you to \"SQUAWK IDENT\". Which transponder function should you activate?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Press the ALT button.", "correctAnswer": "Press the IDENT button.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.2", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 08:51:51.339611", "incorrectAnswer2": "Change the transponder mode to SQUAWK.", "id": "80726bb0-b8e1-425e-8601-e0edf75b0c92", "incorrectAnswer3": "Reset the transponder by setting it to STBY then back to ALT."}, {"question": "You're flying LJC and tower transmits \"Lima-Juliet-Charlie, you're now number two for landing\" (which doesn't require a readback). What is the correct response?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "\"Wilco, Lima-Juliet-Charlie.\"", "correctAnswer": "\"Lima-Juliet-Charlie\"", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(j)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:35:31.115389", "incorrectAnswer2": "\"Number two, roger. Lima-Juliet-Charlie.\"", "id": "f77b6e7d-aef7-4a24-a7af-a59711d3dcb2", "incorrectAnswer3": "\"Affirm\""}, {"question": "When the squelch control is turned all the way up (fully clockwise)", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "almost all signal will be filtered out, including voice transmissions", "correctAnswer": "very little unwanted noise is filtered, and considerable static is likely to be heard", "syllabusReference": "2.4.2", "addedDate": "2022-06-26 10:10:22.187867", "incorrectAnswer2": "only unmodulated signals can be sent", "id": "6e5d9e92-8f62-4fb1-8b4f-3034a1b9ba23", "incorrectAnswer3": "your voice is more likely to be transmitted clearly"}, {"question": "In a lost comms situation you see a steady red light gun signal while in the air, meaning...", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Aerodrome unsafe, do not land", "correctAnswer": "Give way to other aircraft and continue circling", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:42:00.189796", "incorrectAnswer2": "Danger, be on the alert", "id": "d7f50415-684f-4069-b643-4d5b5c5c0061", "incorrectAnswer3": "Return for landing (clearance to land and taxi will be given in due course)"}, {"question": "You're approaching a towered aerodrome and have lost communications. You see a series of alternating red and green flashes from the tower's light gun. What does this mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Give way to other aircraft and continue circling", "correctAnswer": "Danger, be on the alert", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:48:17.864620", "incorrectAnswer2": "Aerodrome unsafe, do not land", "id": "03508313-a07d-431f-86a8-7693549bd3c2", "incorrectAnswer3": "Return for landing (clearance to land and taxi will be given in due course)"}, {"question": "You're taxing at a controlled aerodrome and notice your radio has stopped working. You see a series of white flashes coming from the tower. What does this mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Danger, be on the alert", "correctAnswer": "Return to starting point on aerodrome", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:53:13.249420", "incorrectAnswer2": "Stop", "id": "6d998e64-35e8-4fd6-981a-8d71598b0b66", "incorrectAnswer3": "Cleared for take-off"}, {"question": "Where is it required to operate a transponder transmitting ADS-B data (unless authorised by ATC?)", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "In all airspace in the New Zealand FIR", "correctAnswer": "In transponder mandatory controlled airspace", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 22:49:27.059751", "incorrectAnswer2": "In all transponder mandatory airspace", "id": "1644a25b-5a63-4329-b570-fd68df8b5914", "incorrectAnswer3": "Any time the aircraft begins to move under its own power until it has come to a complete stop at the end of the flight"}, {"question": "What does \"BREAK BREAK\" mean in a radio communication?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Indicates separation of parts of a message to the same aircraft.", "correctAnswer": "Indicates a separation between messages transmitted to different aircraft.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(d)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:31:20.689076", "incorrectAnswer2": "Instructs an aircraft to initiate the \"break\" portion of the standard overhead rejoin.", "id": "d50b3438-c0cb-499d-b96b-9bb18d458003", "incorrectAnswer3": "Instructs an aircraft to immediately alter course to avoid oncoming aircraft traffic."}, {"question": "A boom microphone should be adjusted so that it", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "is above your eyeline so that it picks up other voices in the aircraft cabin", "correctAnswer": "just touches your lips when they are pursed", "syllabusReference": "2.4.4(a)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:30:23.673128", "incorrectAnswer2": "is above your eyeline so as not to interfere with your vision", "id": "623fb73c-adb9-4543-b08f-55ecedef7833", "incorrectAnswer3": "is below your chin, so that your voice is easily picked up by the microphone"}, {"question": "What is the transponder code 1500 used for?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Defence helicopters", "correctAnswer": "Helicopters other than Defence helicopters", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:09:45.308850", "incorrectAnswer2": "For aircraft involved in fire fighting and reconnaissance duties", "id": "b6180843-efb2-41c7-929c-504308dddee2", "incorrectAnswer3": "Powered aircraft in designated general aviation areas"}, {"question": "What does a series of alternating red and green flashes mean when on the ground at an aerodrome?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Stop", "correctAnswer": "Danger, be on the alert", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:53:56.328359", "incorrectAnswer2": "Taxi clear of landing area in use", "id": "4281248d-1a23-4424-a470-1febb4da2bc5", "incorrectAnswer3": "Return to starting point on aerodrome"}, {"question": "Under what conditions are you allowed to enter controlled airspace without an operable transponder?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "If maintaining visual flight rules.", "correctAnswer": "With ATC approval.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.12", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 01:54:06.526184", "incorrectAnswer2": "Never. An operable transponder is always required in controlled airspace.", "id": "9167f7a4-2fdb-4147-9cdf-284484381ff0", "incorrectAnswer3": "Any time when flying below 10,000 AMSL."}, {"question": "What information will a transponder transmit transmitting in Mode C?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Identification (squawk code) and position.", "correctAnswer": "Identification (squawk code), position, and altitude.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.4(b)", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 02:46:21.586866", "incorrectAnswer2": "Identification (squawk code) and altitude only.", "id": "034c55d9-2a64-4455-8142-0fe0366531d6", "incorrectAnswer3": "None, Mode C is only used for TCAS alerts."}, {"question": "You are are flying ZK-ABC and intending to carry out a touch and go on runway 07 at Rangiora aerodrome, which is unattended. You mistakenly transmit \"Rangiora traffic, ABC is downwind zero-seven, full stop.\"  What should you know do?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Transmit: \"Touch and go\"", "correctAnswer": "Transmit: \"Correction, ABC is downwind zero-seven, touch and go\"", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(k)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:33:36.841510", "incorrectAnswer2": "No further transmission is necessary as it will be obvious when you conduct the touch and go that you are not stopping", "id": "5fbf802d-8f7e-4f46-b5df-9c0b314ad111", "incorrectAnswer3": "No correction is necessary as the aerodrome is unattended"}, {"question": "What is the transponder code 2200 used for?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "All aircraft when operating in the aerodrome traffic circuit at a uncontrolled aerodrome", "correctAnswer": "All aircraft when operating in the aerodrome traffic circuit at a controlled aerodrome", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:03:53.217178", "incorrectAnswer2": "Aeroplane traffic operating VFR without an assigned transponder code", "id": "5a796096-4da1-4d51-826e-72e33962179d", "incorrectAnswer3": "All aircraft operating VFR in the Auckland Oceanic FIR only"}, {"question": "What transponder code means \"in flight emergency\"?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "7600", "correctAnswer": "7700", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:13:22.164027", "incorrectAnswer2": "7500", "id": "8b410e55-6aef-4183-8fd6-a17a88ca385a", "incorrectAnswer3": "1111"}, {"question": "You're on the ground at a towered aerodrome with an inoperative radio, and see a steady green light gun signal. What does this mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Cleared to taxi", "correctAnswer": "Cleared for take-off", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:49:52.612399", "incorrectAnswer2": "Return to starting point on aerodrome", "id": "e66eb58d-3ccf-4255-9b3a-e0da22d42da9", "incorrectAnswer3": "Taxi clear of landing area in use"}, {"question": "Following a forced landing in a remote area, you should;", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Ensure the ELT is ON. It's safe to turn the ELT off after approximately 10 minutes to conserve battery, because this will have given the RCCNZ centre long enough to locate the signal.", "correctAnswer": "Ensure the ELT is ON, and leave it ON until rescued.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.8", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 02:56:51.247001", "incorrectAnswer2": "Set the ELT to ARM. Only change the ELT to ON when rescue personnel are in the vicinity.", "id": "280c00a0-6021-4d25-a5a2-06ae8d01d0d4", "incorrectAnswer3": "Disable the ELT to prevent any risk of an electrical fire."}, {"question": "What is the correct phraseology for an initial call from ZK-LJJ to Christchurch Tower?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "\"Lima Juliet Juliet, Christchurch Tower\"", "correctAnswer": "\"Christchurch tower, Lima Juliet Juliet\"", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(f)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:01:46.248825", "incorrectAnswer2": "\"Christchurch tower, response requested\"", "id": "8a586527-5509-4366-a0b6-01697c368dd0", "incorrectAnswer3": "\"Lima Juliet Juliet, how do you read?\""}, {"question": "When flying at the boundary between two different classes of airspace, you must comply with the requirements of...", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "The more restrictive class of airspace.", "correctAnswer": "The less restrictive class of airspace.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(c)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:34:20.444989", "incorrectAnswer2": "The more restrictive class of airspace, unless operating with VFR flight following.", "id": "7fd11fa9-912d-4635-bd7c-14e09f0934fa", "incorrectAnswer3": "The less restrictive class of airspace, unless operating in a formation flight."}, {"question": "What is the correct pronunciation of \"5\" in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Five", "correctAnswer": "Fife", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(c)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:18:17.645801", "incorrectAnswer2": "Fif", "id": "b39acaa2-698a-40fd-a8eb-a3d77b92ec2d", "incorrectAnswer3": "Flight"}, {"question": "What does Readability Four mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Readable now and then", "correctAnswer": "Readable", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(m)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:44:01.936491", "incorrectAnswer2": "Readable, but with difficulty", "id": "2590e31f-f5d7-4654-ac83-1aa7d04c9e98", "incorrectAnswer3": "Perfectly readable"}, {"question": "What does Readability One mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Readable now and then", "correctAnswer": "Unreadable", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(m)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:42:18.318710", "incorrectAnswer2": "Readable, but with difficulty", "id": "a9639be9-6f0c-44b2-a818-24dce6648c22", "incorrectAnswer3": "Readable"}, {"question": "What does a steady red light gun signal mean when on the ground?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Taxi clear of landing area in use", "correctAnswer": "Stop", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:50:27.367412", "incorrectAnswer2": "Return to starting point on aerodrome", "id": "65fb6cff-f485-44f6-b10a-7823bb6069b8", "incorrectAnswer3": "Danger, be on the alert"}, {"question": "You're flying outside of controlled airspace in your non-military Cessna 172, and haven't been assigned a transponder code by ATC. What transponder code should you use?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "2000", "correctAnswer": "1200", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:02:02.895996", "incorrectAnswer2": "7700", "id": "911dea18-ffa3-452f-b427-3136e5107844", "incorrectAnswer3": "1300"}, {"question": "What does Readability Three mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Unreadable.", "correctAnswer": "Readable, but with difficulty.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(m)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:43:12.295600", "incorrectAnswer2": "Readable now and then.", "id": "32162798-4c3d-4244-8e43-5ba85939619e", "incorrectAnswer3": "Readable."}, {"question": "What does the term \"listening watch\" mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Identifying traffic both through visual and audio methods.", "correctAnswer": "Tuning the designated frequency and staying alert for any mention of your callsign.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(l)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:39:12.571602", "incorrectAnswer2": "A special type of watch used to improve audio perception.", "id": "9bbd8f4d-7a51-4450-8bc1-1337f179df25", "incorrectAnswer3": "Always tuning the emergency frequency 121.5MHz."}, {"question": "The time system used in aviation is;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Uncoordinated Time Constant", "correctAnswer": "Co-ordinated universal time", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(e)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:32:53.615724", "incorrectAnswer2": "Universal Time Constant", "id": "4443d4c3-86db-4ff5-a4a3-75421813f794", "incorrectAnswer3": "Local Mean Time"}, {"question": "A UNICOM service is;", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "staffed by Airways staff at uncontrolled aerodromes", "correctAnswer": "staffed by non-Airways staff at uncontrolled aerodromes", "syllabusReference": "2.10.6(a)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:35:05.343842", "incorrectAnswer2": "staffed by Airways staff at controlled aerodromes", "id": "f40a73e6-a47e-457d-9ac8-dd5c67976601", "incorrectAnswer3": "staffed by non-Airways staff at controlled aerodromes"}, {"question": "How can an automatic ELT be activated manually?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "By setting the remote ELT switch to the \"ARM\" position.", "correctAnswer": "By setting the remote ELT switch to the \"ON\" position.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.6(b)", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 02:50:08.815845", "incorrectAnswer2": "Automatic ELTs aren't able to be activated manually.", "id": "458f72f0-ff3c-4a67-b40d-8d51e8635f66", "incorrectAnswer3": "By activating \"ARM\" mode directly on the ELT unit."}, {"question": "What is the correct pronunciation of \"decimal\" in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Decimal", "correctAnswer": "Day-see-mal", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(c)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:19:23.667280", "incorrectAnswer2": "Dot", "id": "72de90f3-88c8-4987-9a50-77b85632e970", "incorrectAnswer3": "Point"}, {"question": "What does the phrase \"How do you read?\" mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Confirm ready to copy clearance.", "correctAnswer": "What is the readability of my transmission?", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(d)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:45:27.016087", "incorrectAnswer2": "Do you have charts available for the aerodrome?", "id": "a494eef3-41ec-4a35-bbb3-d8805c0bc1b8", "incorrectAnswer3": "Are you able to comply with my last transmission?"}, {"question": "You're on the ground at a towered aerodrome and see a series of green flashes from the tower's light gun, meaning...", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Cleared for take-off", "correctAnswer": "Cleared to taxi", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:51:22.708117", "incorrectAnswer2": "Taxi clear of landing area in use", "id": "813a3905-c0db-4669-8cd6-053f186e111d", "incorrectAnswer3": "Return to starting point on aerodrome"}, {"question": "What is the correct way to transmit a callsign for a Cessna Skyhawk, with tail number ZK-XYP?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Cessna Zulu Kilo", "correctAnswer": "Cardinal Xray-Yankee-Papa", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(i)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 09:16:14.638953", "incorrectAnswer2": "Cessna Xray-Yankee-Piper", "id": "9bf6d48f-bbff-4bf3-a31c-c6fb437e864f", "incorrectAnswer3": "Cessna Cardinal Zulu-Kilo-Xray-Yankee-Papa"}, {"question": "What squawk code should be used by powered aircraft in designated General Aviation Areas (GAAs)?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "1200", "correctAnswer": "1400", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:07:28.562508", "incorrectAnswer2": "1300", "id": "754b6b8c-d984-4e7e-b9da-d6aebf567f5f", "incorrectAnswer3": "2200"}, {"question": "As pilot-in-command, which statement is true about the preflight action required for communication/navigation facilities?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "You must check the status of all communication and navigation facilities within 50NM of your flight path.", "correctAnswer": "You must check the status of any communication and navigation facilities intended to be used.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(a)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:21:50.333225", "incorrectAnswer2": "You are only required to check the status of a communication facility if no alternative facility exists on your flight path.", "id": "3f9a4318-fb2b-4ef6-8b5f-35dd87e81c00", "incorrectAnswer3": "You are only required to check the status of navigation facilities if using VOR navigation."}, {"question": "How can you verify whether an ELT has been activated?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "The ELT will switch from ARM to the EMERG mode.", "correctAnswer": "A red flashing light on the ELT, and a siren signal being broadcast on 121.5 MHz.", "syllabusReference": "2.8.12", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 00:56:29.387039", "incorrectAnswer2": "A red flashing light on the ELT, and a siren signal broadcast on 119.1 MHz.", "id": "bae9a7ef-4c16-4135-bccc-dca6db5340ee", "incorrectAnswer3": "The transponder will automatically squawk 7700."}, {"question": "You are enroute to land at Dunedin airport and, having obtained a clearance, have entered the control zone.  As you approach downwind your radio stops working. You notice that the control tower is shining a steady red light at you. What does this mean?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Leave the control zone without delay", "correctAnswer": "Give way to other traffic and continue in the circuit", "syllabusReference": "2.16.10", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:41:55.111575", "incorrectAnswer2": "Aerodrome unsafe - Do not land", "id": "1a482bf2-a17d-41b6-8a19-3e88bbe25812", "incorrectAnswer3": "Danger - be on the alert"}, {"question": "When preflighting an aircraft with an automatic ELT, what position should the remote ELT switch be in before starting a normal flight?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "ON", "correctAnswer": "ARM", "syllabusReference": "2.8.6(b)", "addedDate": "2022-07-09 02:51:57.716551", "incorrectAnswer2": "OFF", "id": "1deb7047-dfcc-44eb-855e-47eb7b9a53f1", "incorrectAnswer3": "STBY"}, {"question": "How should the letter \"U\" be said in a radio transmission?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Unicorn", "correctAnswer": "Uniform", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-07 21:13:19.772737", "incorrectAnswer2": "Yu", "id": "d7dd480f-7a4d-4bab-8ca8-15517f09199f", "incorrectAnswer3": "Union"}, {"question": "What does a series of red flashes mean when on the ground at an aerodrome?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Stop", "correctAnswer": "Taxi clear of landing area in use", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:51:58.968133", "incorrectAnswer2": "Danger, be on the alert", "id": "e241baa2-07f4-44f6-b22b-925b846e6da2", "incorrectAnswer3": "Return to starting point on aerodrome"}, {"question": "When a transponder is in standby (STBY) mode, which of the following is true?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "The transponder transmits only identification and position information.", "correctAnswer": "The transponder is on, but won't respond to interrogation.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.2", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 08:54:33.884546", "incorrectAnswer2": "The transponder transmits altitude, but not position information.", "id": "5a876113-3f1f-4920-8ecc-5da71ee45cb0", "incorrectAnswer3": "The transponder transmits only the identification (squawk code) when interrogated."}, {"question": "Your radio is inop, and you see a steady green light as you approach the aerodrome. What does this mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Give way to other aircraft and continue circling", "correctAnswer": "Cleared to land", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:40:25.709594", "incorrectAnswer2": "Return for landing (clearance to land and taxi will be given in due course)", "id": "2f0d15cf-ba68-4a3f-874e-67632ac33ba8", "incorrectAnswer3": "Land at this aerodrome and proceed to apron"}, {"question": "What is the correct way to transmit the time \"1020\"?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Ten twenty", "correctAnswer": "One zero two zero", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(e)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:55:16.078036", "incorrectAnswer2": "Four zero before", "id": "40c680ad-4e07-48f1-bd3c-c4d546b97d73", "incorrectAnswer3": "One zero twenty"}, {"question": "What does a series of white flashes from a light gun mean?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Cleared to land", "correctAnswer": "Land at this aerodrome and proceed to apron", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(b)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:46:39.447534", "incorrectAnswer2": "Give way to other aircraft and continue circling", "id": "2542af02-bab7-42da-84fc-ff5bcbb4a932", "incorrectAnswer3": "Danger, be on the alert"}, {"question": "When flying in Class B, C, or D airspace...", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Two-way communications are required with the ATC unit responsible for the airspace, unless flying on an IFR flight plan.", "correctAnswer": "Two-way communications are required with the ATC unit responsible for the airspace, unless authorised.", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(c)", "addedDate": "2023-01-27 20:32:09.522571", "incorrectAnswer2": "Two-way communications are always required with the ATC unit responsible for the airspace.", "id": "bfcbd816-1435-42aa-b5ad-429e41aeb8ce", "incorrectAnswer3": "Two-way communications are required with the ATC unit responsible for the airspace, unless flying an aircraft equipped with dual ADSB transmitters."}, {"question": "What information will a transponder transmit transmitting in Mode A?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Identification (squawk code), position, and altitude.", "correctAnswer": "Identification (squawk code) and position.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.4(a)", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 02:44:28.703669", "incorrectAnswer2": "Identification (squawk code), position, and IDENT.", "id": "f053e42b-a68b-4a7b-8560-dc5ec7cf6d1c", "incorrectAnswer3": "IDENT and altitude."}, {"question": "What term is used to indicate an error was made in a previous communication, and the correct information follows?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Alteration", "correctAnswer": "Correction", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(d)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:33:19.772423", "incorrectAnswer2": "Modification", "id": "ac1a55f5-7698-4001-88ec-0cad49751412", "incorrectAnswer3": "Reconfirm"}, {"question": "How would you select Mode A on a transponder?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Select the \"STBY\" (standby) setting.", "correctAnswer": "Select the \"ON\" setting.", "syllabusReference": "2.6.2", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 09:11:39.367465", "incorrectAnswer2": "Select the \"ALT\" (altitude) setting.", "id": "27eab44c-ab23-4a54-b382-9f51b4468d7d", "incorrectAnswer3": "Select the \"TST\" (test) setting."}, {"question": "What transponder code is used by Defence helicopters?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "6000", "correctAnswer": "6500", "syllabusReference": "2.10.4(d)", "addedDate": "2023-02-08 23:10:53.755685", "incorrectAnswer2": "0111", "id": "ed533572-a927-4125-ab1c-8360a61bb92f", "incorrectAnswer3": "2200"}, {"question": "You are flying towards an airfield where you intend to land. As you are just about to enter the MBZ in which your destination airfield is located, your radio fails completely. What should you do?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Continue to your original destination airfield", "correctAnswer": "Divert to an aerodrome outside the MBZ", "syllabusReference": "2.16.4(c)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:39:22.890549", "incorrectAnswer2": "Transmit a PAN PAN call", "id": "851822cf-464d-4cd5-bb47-e337e1b9a953", "incorrectAnswer3": "Divert to the nearest controlled aerodrome and squawk 7700"}, {"question": "What is the correct term to use in a radio transmission meaning \"yes\"?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Wilco", "correctAnswer": "Affirm", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(d)", "addedDate": "2023-01-13 21:28:36.548261", "incorrectAnswer2": "Roger", "id": "2ee105f2-70da-4f41-8e73-5be6b4c76a58", "incorrectAnswer3": "Yes"}, {"question": "How should the time 8:03am be transmitted when using an aviation radio?", "authorName": "", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "eight zero three a-m", "correctAnswer": "zero eight zero three", "syllabusReference": "2.10.2(c)", "addedDate": "2021-10-09 02:32:33.575670", "incorrectAnswer2": "zero three a-m", "id": "a8a3d26a-112b-4cf0-8239-34099927d9f5", "incorrectAnswer3": "zero three a-m U-T-C"}, {"question": "If ATC instructs you to \"STOP SQUAWKING ALTITUDE\", what should you do?", "authorName": "kp", "examId": "ppl-3", "incorrectAnswer1": "Set the transponder mode to \"ALT\" (Mode C).", "correctAnswer": "Set the transponder mode to \"ON\" (Mode A).", "syllabusReference": "2.6.8", "addedDate": "2022-07-02 09:32:36.419133", "incorrectAnswer2": "Set the transponder mode to \"ON\" (Mode C).", "id": "5bcfd9b4-79e1-4ea2-b0b5-75e9590e831e", "incorrectAnswer3": "Set the transponder mode to \"ALT\" (Mode A)."}
    ]

print(len(results))
